MUGDHA CHOUDHARY

SR VENDOR MANAGEMENT ASSOCIATE PHONE I (+91) 8076716193

EMAIL I mugdhachoudhary02@g

mail.com

LOCATION I Noida, Gurgaon delhi

bengaluru pune, INDIA

EXPERIENCE I 8 Years 0 Month

Key Skills

- Accounts Handling
- Lead Qualification
- German Language
- Excel
- MS Office
- Vendor Management
- Internet
- Catalog Management
- Amazon
- Catalog Creation
- Digital Strategy
- Operations Management
- Category Management
- Brand Strategy
- Catalog

Certification

Digital Marketing

Languages

German

Profile Summary

As a Account management associate responsible for lead generation and pre sales, correct & enhanced catalog of brands/labels, improvement of storefront, performing extensive brand research to identify new brands for onboard, SLA adherence for assigned tasks. Worked with multiple cross functional teams like vendor manager, quality team, Tech team on various projects. Connect with different vendors. Onboarding of vendors. Account management of vendors and sellers

Work Experience

Sr vendor management associate

Amazon

10/2018 - Present

senior vendor recruiter senior catalog analyst

Sr. Catalog Associate

Amazon

10/2018 - 10/2018

Retail vendor recruiter brand researcher

dan net pvt. ltd.

11/2015 - 02/2017

customer service

Customer Care Executive

11/2013 - 11/2015

Education

M.A - English 2013 na

B.A - English
2017
Indira Gandhi National Open University
(IGNOU)